It's the morning chime, and it's us.
CJBiSH.
Let's play the cuz game!
Let's play!
Today we are going to play a game called Nanja Monja.
Have any of you ever played this game before?
Yes, I have.
Then, Yuma, please explain.
Yes, sir.
First, you draw cards from this deck one by one.
Then, you'll see a special person like this.
There are many kinds of people.
You name them.
You can name them yourself, for example
Something like "Oyatsu-san"...
Yamafuji
No...
Hara-san becomes Yamato
And then I start to draw more and more.
Then, if this Kao-chan draws, Kao-chan becomes this.
Then Murata
Murata
As you continue to draw, they become more and more the same.
Ah, it comes out.
When it comes out...
It's too early.
Name it.
And after this time, you yell it out.
The person who was the first to yell it
I see.
Yes, sir.
All the cards.
All of them.
You can have all the cards you've ever had.
I'll tell you when I've accumulated enough cards.
It's okay.
Yes, it's okay.
Whoever has the most cards wins.
Oh, wow.
Some people put really long cards.
I see.
Some kind of splurge.
It's all about imagination and stuff.
Memory
Memory.
Yeah.
I'm going to cut the card.
I'll cut it out.
Tempo?
I'll cut the cards.
This will be cut.
Let's have them play rock-paper-scissors-paper, starting with the winner.
First one is "goo" rock-paper-scissors.
Yes, sir.
Show
Show.
Shaw.
You won.
We lost.
I won.
Oh, I'm always too manly.
We won.
I won!
Rock, paper, scissors!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
rock, paper, scissors!
It's aiko, right?
Wow, I won!
So then...
Let's go.
Okay.
Okay, I'm going.
I did this the first time.
I'm sure that's what it is.
Two.
Here she is.
Let's see...
John Bijot.
John V jot
John V
John V.
I think I'm going to tell the dog.
johnbjotv5
John V
Next, your guys.
Uh, well, John V jot
Thirteen.
John VJOT 13.
Thirteens. This is, uh, this is, uh, this is the 13th generation when two people come together.
Yes, um...
Croissant.
Simple.
What was that?
Oh, I don't get it.
Oh, I don't understand.
When I put it on myself, I...
Oh, uh...
Uh...
Foot, long, long, long.
Legs, long, long, long.
Face, tiny.
Leg, long, long, long
Face, tiny
Ah!
Here.
Mr. Pumpkina
The wall.
Simple.
Fireball.
Indeed.
Oh, like Hirabiya.
Oh, I missed it!
I didn't see it!
Oh, forget it, I missed it.
And he just ran off.
I missed.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
I'm forgetting everything we've been through.
I thought you said it was John something.
Orange twing.
Orange twinging?
Orange twinging.
That's easy to see.
Here you go.
Oh, 13th.
Thirteen?
No, sir.
Fifth generation.
Fifth generation?
Then you're right.
Fifth generation.
But there's a difference.
You're a great godfather.
You're a godfather.
Yeah.
Here we go.
What should we name her?
Let's go with Tate-eda.
Tate-eda.
The orange twin.
Ah!
You're right, you're right, you're right.
All I can think of is "ah.
Uh...
Aww.
It just feels good.
Uh, orange twin.
Uh...
Uh-oh.
That's a tough one.
Edamame, please.
Edamame.
Ahh.
Let's see...
Thank you for watching.
Yes, you made me smile.
You made me smile.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm the type of person who piles it all on top of each other in tiny little pieces.
Tiny.
Oh, it's fun!
It's fun!
When I went to Juke today...
Hannøen also folded Lisa always mountain ah
And so once Cornell Lil greetings
What a PR what?
It's the gear that makes Von.
That's not what I mean. I'm here.
Who are you, what do you do?
What do you do?
Group G Operation!
Tuna face, please, election campaign manager!
Barefoot!
Yes, yes, John, I'm a private citizen.
I don't know.
Male
Oh, he had long legs and a long face.
Impossible!
He had long legs and a face.
Thank you very much.
Here we go.
Oh, you're in the fourth grade?
I'm 16.
Oh, yeah.
Sixteen.
That's great. I'm gonna start naming them.
I can't remember.
You're right.
I only named the wall.
Here you go, toy.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Oh, me?
Me?
I don't know what's going on.
Ready, go!
The wall.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, okay.
Oh, John.
You're 16, Jung-min.
You're good at this!
You love 16-year-olds.
The same person who's been writing more and more...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
There aren't that many 8-year-olds.
There are a lot of 8-year-olds.
There's a lot of 8-year-olds in the whole country.
In the world.
Yes, uh, I don't know.
Fireball.
Oh, yeah.
I just put that on there.
That means you don't know.
That means you don't know!
Yes, oh, that... that...
John Mijon and 6 years old... No, no, no, no, 5 years old.
No, no, no.
Thirteen? Huh?
Three years old with John Mijon.
Five? Not exactly.
Five? A little different.
A little different.
Five, 13, 16.
Okay.
Yes. Oh, what's that?
Oh, that's fast.
That's fast. That's fast.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, that?
John Mijon and 16 years old.
Is this the front page of Lena's book?
It's the only one I can get.
Come on.
Oh, what's that?
John Mijon and 16 years old.
Sorry, hey.
Sorry, just a minute.
Oh, oh, here.
Ah, ah, ah, ah
Mister's leg
Uh, leg leg
Legs. Legs.
Seriously?
Yes, uh...
Eight years old.
Okay.
That's it for the show.
What was that?
Close!
I put some color on it.
My eyes are glazed over.
Not at all.
Long, long legs!
Small face!
Eyes!
Head bash!
Hit your head, Kao-chan!
Okay!
Go ahead!
No more new cards?
Then put in the one you already know!
Ready!
Here you go!
Smile card!
I like the wall!
The wall!
Fireball!
This one's not gonna sell either.
Here you go!
Long, long legs!
Small face!
Small face, uncle!
You're so tiny!
For the first time, I'm in a small face
And they named him after me!
One more?
Two more.
Seino
Joby shot, 16 cm.
I knew it!
I knew you could sneak up on me.
Oh, no.
Let's go.
Ready, set, go!
Closter.
Look at me.
Look at the green part.
I think that was a pretty good game.
I think.
You want me to put it down?
One, two.
One, two, three.
Eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty.
Thank you.
The winner here was Kaho.
I want to play the second round in Generation Nanjya mode.
Certainly.
Now.
Now?
Right now.
We're doing it again.
You're doing it again.
I'm doing it again.
Reset the name and do it again.
Reset your name.
I miss name reset.
Let's do a second round.
Let's get this over with.
Next round.
So...
We've finished the first round.
I'd like to do it again...
Um...
I'd like to make a half of Necard's mountain noodle.
Only half of it.
It's a short version.
again as an extra.
I'd like to see it!
All the names I just gave you
I'll give them new names.
Yes, sir.
Okay, then.
Starting with the first champion.
I'd like to start with the first champion.
Yes, sir.
And the cologne?
Oh, my God, that name just came up.
Pumpkin's name just popped up.
It's not the same thing.
Jamboree.
Poipoi poipoi poipoi
Jamboree
So fast.
Strong. The champion, after all.
I like this one.
From the first time.
There's chemistry in this.
Oh, no, it's not.
The other one.
What was that?
Mr. Yaeda.
Mr. Potato.
McCrory.
Mr. Potato Paccholi
Mr. Potato McCrory
These are delicious together, though.
Yes, please.
Yes, Don.
Here you go.
Tsuru Tsuru Tenjiro.
Crane Tenjiro.
Tenjiro Crane
Tsuru Tsuru Tenjiro
Interesting
LOL!
It's more difficult than before.
It's getting harder.
Oh, it's okay.
Nudge, nudge, nudge.
You were trying to drive me crazy earlier.
Refractive eye shadow.
Oh, it's new again.
Inner thigh bumps.
Just going with the look.
Ready, go.
Different one.
Well, I don't know what to do.
Where are your hands?
You.
I'm curious.
Where are your hands?
I care.
I'm curious
Where are your hands?
Taro
Taro and Jiro
Like "Pokkori Jiro.
Like "Dokkkiri Jiro".
I'm back.
This is Taro
This is Taro.
Jiro, did you say?
Like Tenjiro?
Slippery Tenjiro.
I'm in trouble.
Oh...
This is...
Dermatologist, live!
Live.
Dermatology, live.
Dermatology, live and let live!
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
I've got a lot of stuff on my plate.
I'm using a good eyeshadow.
I'll use it.
Oh, it's good.
It's delicious.
This is jojoba, jojoba, jojoba.
I remember.
Brief mofu mofu
Brief moh-moh-moh.
But it's easy to write.
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh! I didn't know you were here.
This is my first time.
I like hats.
I like hats, I like hats, I like hats, I like hats, I like hats, I like hats
Yes, you sure seem to like it
Oh, I'm in.
Chupa.
Chupa lollipops.
Here we go.
Pop.
Oh, what am I going to do?
What was that outfit you were wearing earlier?
Okay, Kazuyo.
Kazuyo
You, which way is your hand?
I'm curious.
Lou.
S
Kalon
Caron.
Oh!
Strong strong strong strong
Here we go.
Inner window, this way.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Amazing.
That's Natzke's parents.
Good night.
I love, love, love hats.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's not good night.
Good night.
Aaah, uit, puh-puh-puh-puh-puh-puh-puh-puh-puh-puh-puh-puh-puh-puh-puh.
If I miss, I'll be Mr. Nice and the car...
I don't know if there's something in here, but I'm looking for a good color.
What are these?
What is this?
Green, indeed.
You're a sweetheart, aren't you?
Yes, a hemsigamo.
Here you go.
This time.
You're right, it's got a little bit of a squeak.
And the name, too.
It's funny because it's long.
Okay, here we go.
You're in my head.
Jamboree.
New
Mr. Nagao
Certainly.
I'll go.
Mr. Uchimura
Yay!
I'll try the Christmas tteokbokki.
Mr. Potato
I'm going to eat a snack from a convenience store
I got out of the potato with the tteokbokki
Then I'll eat them here
I'll try the snacks.
Oh, thank you.
You were at the dermatologist's.
I was at the dermatologist's office.
Well, good.
You're the one who was in the dermatologist's office.
I'll take you to the dermatologist.
Dermatologist, that's what I want you to do.
I want you to stay at the dermatologist's.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, I'm sorry...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Chapa-chapa.
Candy.
Uh...
Let's go.
Yes, ma'am.
Stay in the dermatologist's office.
You have to stay in the dermatology department.
Stay in the dermatology department!
Let's go for it!
I've been saying you've got to stay in dermatology for a while now.
Here you go.
I like hats, I like hats, I like hats, I like hats, I like hats, I like hats...
I like hats, I like hats, I like hats, I like hats, I like hats, I like hats
Oh, I like hats.
I like hats, I like hats, I like hats, I like hats, I like hats.
Uh-oh.
Okay.
You coming?
I don't know anyone.
We have to name it.
It was difficult... and that was the end of it.
Here we go again.
Okay.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Nine.
Ooh!
Ooh
Ooh.
Thank you very much.
And the winner of the exhibition match was
Kaho.
Thank you very much.
So...
How was it?
Really, it was such a fun game.
I'm very happy to have played it.
I'm going to keep on naming them
Let's keep on stepping on it!
I hope you'll all give it a try.
I hope you'll give it a try.
The second edition, you know, as the winner.
As the winner.
That's right.
Next time, you'll have to beat Kaho Kobayashi.
Next time, too, as a great person
I'd like to participate.
I look forward to working with you.
So, here it is
Good button and
Subscribe to our channel
And please leave a comment!
Bye, bye, bye.